quality-website-traffic.com 2019-02-27

# Quality Website Traffic - Get Quality Traffic to Your Website for FREE

**Privacy Policy:**

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. 

**What information is collected?**

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you will be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with your experience. 

**How the collected information is used?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site or enter information on our site.  We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter,

respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways: 

• To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested. 

• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature. 

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information. 

**Linking to third-party sites:**

We may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. Users can visit our site anonymously.

**Privacy policy changes:**

You will be notified by email of any Privacy Policy changes.

**Updating your information:  **

You can change your personal information or delete your account by logging in to your account.

**We use cookies:**

As is common practice with almost all professional websites this site uses cookies, which are tiny files that are downloaded to your computer, to improve your experience. Disabling these cookies from being stored may downgrade or 'break' certain elements of the sites functionality.  We use these cookies to provide a better service to you.

**Security:**

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur: 

We will notify you via email 

• Within 3 business days 

  **CAN SPAM Act  **

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.   
We collect your email address in order to:   
• Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.   
To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:   
• Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.   
• Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.   
• Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.   
• Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.   
• Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.   
• Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at   
• Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email. and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

quality-website-traffic.com No.515, 1/134, rajkumar garden Chennai, Tamil nadu-603112, India

pakachu3@gmail.com

Copyright © 2019. Quality Website Traffic. All rights reserved.
